Copyright from SI Media
Pap.
Mom. I get breakfast?
Honey, you do not move.
- Mommy, Daddy!
Get up.
I love you!
So many knees.
- Upcoming!
Okay, yes. Charlie,
I'll make you over breakfast.
I am ... awake.
Here we go.
- It begins.
I get pizza for breakfast?
- Yes.
Really?
- No.
Charlotte, come from that chair.
- No chance.
I count to three.
- No, Mom.
Here we go again.
- A ...
two, three ...
- Mom!
Used you count back?
- It works every time.
I am beginning to lunches.
A: Change.
That subtracting 42.
We can give back about $ 600.
You're kidding?
- Really?
Anyway.
- You turn it on!
I like you do!
- Good thing you're happy.
We go kiteboarding in Spain.
How sexy is that?
A Roth IRA begin
That's seksier.
We can not but 20 times
on the beach doing.
I think that is better.
Would you do it, no?
A fruitful idea.
As you can see there
the floor in oak.
Typical was this house
at 1.8 million ...
but now only 320,000.
It drops down even.
- I think.
Wait is indeed better.
Hello, my people.
I like the Fosters.
Play Lego with me.
- First a small coma ...
and then we keep it
best Lego battle ever.
How you doing, Fosters?
- Hi, Katy.
All right next door?
- A babysitter is needed, right?
Is not it date night?
- Yeah, right, thanks for coming.
We go on date night.
- You're too tired, baby.
No, I looked quite
the week off.
Unless you're too tired?
- No, it'll be fun.
We're going good, right?
We go.
Taste the puree with salmon you?
- Yes, very. Thanks.
On Sunday, Ollie
his friend Hayden a party.
Do I 'm sure a gift?
- Yes, but nothing about China ...
nothing with batteries ...
I take it differently now.
What story is behind it?
Third date. The first
well, the second a disaster ...
She gives him a chance,
to show that he is not boring.
And he fails.
'I have a potato on my fork.
I like to eat potatoes ...
they are delicious ...
but I never stop
actually in my mouth. "
Not for me, Jeremy,
but I'm going home now ...
for winds to pick up a shoe box.
That is nonsense.
Look at love.
First appointment.
- No, he's got a ring.
No, married?
They are on the same side.
Bragging is.
- How to talk to each other.
Twisting your neck.
"Hi, how you doing? Good. "
Wedding Rings, definitely.
This is a kid friendly place.
Coffee or dessert for you tonight?
What do you think?
I am so tired when I got my
head on the table would put ...
For 'n years would sleep.
No, only the account.
Where earlier today
DA Frank Crenshaw an ...
Hey, I wait in the sport.
- I promised the city ...
for its clean streets.
Let me tell you something.
This broom and I ...
not break our promises.
- I 'm going to sleep.
I'm so there.
- Book Club tomorrow.
We break them!
What 'oh'?
You put your foot bracket,
which means that we do not ...
You know.
- No, we can still mad.
Only if you feel like it.
- With all my heart, yes.
I will bring him here ...
I do not mind
if we do not.
No, I ... Very happy.
I need me here on set.
No, it does not matter.
- You sure?
For by those potatoes
I am what windy.
We turn one on.
- You sure?
I will brighten your life.
Next time.
We make a quick tunes.
- What?
A fast tunes.
A quickie.
I can quickly ...
- Yes, it is good.
Nasran her feet and breasts
members when they went through the desert.
Blood dripped down her leg
the ground ...
leaving a large red stain
emptiness of living.
This part really appealed to me.
Walking 20 miles for water ...
and then discover that you
menstruating.
I could not stop crying.
- Ibid. Literally.
Best pathetic.
- Best sad?
You do not have any clue
what it is to show a teenage girl to ...
her first period
and that the rule of the Taliban.
That is correct.
And neither will you.
But ...
- Can you help me?
Yeah, thanks. Excuse me.
My God.
Do you have your period now?
- Yes.
This should really read.
A girl with her period in the wilderness.
Why do you do that still.
That is married.
Things you do not want.
I do not.
- How so?
Haley and I are apart.
But you are happy.
- No, not really.
Why do we
the book club here in your house?
I can not tell the kids.
Keep it to yourself until
I make it public.
Tell Claire.
- Yes, yes.
And how come?
- I thought everything was fine ...
Really. But we are stuck
in a role.
As Asian in Sixteen Candles,
Long Dog Dick.
Long Duk Dong.
- That guy.
Gedde Watanabe.
- He who can not play ...
How hard he tries.
He can not play doctor.
No, Long Duk Dong would
disguised as a doctor.
Exactly! And that's us.
We are not a couple anymore,
just ...
good roommates.
Better than excellent.
- Haley is down injured.
And I bet they
mind will change.
My best decision ever.
I've never been happier.
I can do what I want.
Dance.
If you have
The last dance?
No idea, our marriage?
- I want to dance every night.
And I want my top take off
and make do with three guys.
Three at once?
A nightmare.
This is literally a repeated
stress that I have.
What do you want?
- We know each other too well.
Always the same conversation,
same schedule ...
sex twice a week
in the same position.
Twice a week?
- Yes, so rare.
Yes, rare. Therefore
I was so surprised.
You seem much Naserin.
This is not true.
- Yes it is.
Why is it all about me?
You are the one going crazy ...
You're like Naserin because you feel ashamed
how exciting you are.
You deserve to feel sexy.
And you have a bird rounds.
- The metaphor I do not understand.
It is not ...
- I'm still alive ...
We have a date tomorrow.
- Good.
Enjoy the puree and salmon.
A bird rounds.
Get that bird away.
Hi, baby.
Hi, guys.
What did you learn today?
- Nothing.
Fantastic.
Waiting for the high school.
Who'll win?
- Want something else wear?
No, I think ...
I ... You look beautiful.
I did this only briefly,
it's stupid ...
No, you look fantastic.
I ...
I'm going to change clothes and show a shower.
We would not miss the movie.
- Or a movie?
What do you think of a
dinner in the city?
We should not.
- Yes.
Forward. In 10 minutes ready.
I show you ...
to the new Sea-Food
take place ...
Claw? Do you get outside.
And the city is so far away.
- No.
You tell your potential customers are not
it's only 20 minutes far?
Yes, I lie. It's an hour.
- If we go on ...
ten minutes we are there for
seven and we show a table.
Yes? Say yes. Yes.
- Yes.
I do it.
How you doing?
- Names, please.
We have no reservation.
- We did not connect.
We crowded.
- We thought early to ...
and then a table.
Not met, huh.
- No.
Are there free tables?
- Yes ...
There are people who months
Book in advance ...
and it is 6:30 p.m. Friday
on the beautiful Island of Manhattan ...
So ... No.
We are on a date and
We wanted a special evening ...
So we ask you or your
have a free table?
Wait at the bar
and if a table is released ...
I come get you.
- Thanks.
Bye bye.
- We're there.
I had you already forgotten.
With Claw, welcome.
We are not the only one without a table.
I think we are lucky to have.
Good night.
- No idea what you are talking about.
Thanks. Very nice.
- Drink?
Yes, something with a great garnish,
because I am so hungry.
Hello.
Two Chardonnay, please.
He's just distracted.
- Are we going elsewhere?
No, give it some time.
- Tripplehorn ...
table 2.
I want the night otherwise.
So do I. But it is so difficult.
Table 2.
- Return.
No, we're fine.
- This place is not 'us'.
Table 2. Tripplehorn?
What do you think of Tina Tavern,
a cozy table for two.
It's okay, really.
- No, it's not.
Tripplehorn, table 2!
We!
We are Tripplehorn.
- Great.
This way.
What are you doing, Phil?
- Trust me.
This should not.
- And here we are.
Can I take your coats?
- Yeah, thanks.
Enjoy your meal.
- Thanks.
Look at this table.
- Honey ...
No, honey. The Tripplehorn's
did not come.
Who are we angry?
Let us relax ...
and enjoy their seafood.
Or I suck on a napkin.
Holy ... Check prices.
If we pay so much for crab,
best he can sing, dance ...
and our proposals
The Little Mermaid.
So one great evening.
Brings no accident as
cheers to you 'n empty glass?
I think not.
I would change our children
for such a life like this.
You're so mean.
- It would be cool.
What's the story?
He's a successful manager ...
and she gets drunk enough
for all that later, to endure.
Because he likes weird things.
He goes with her hair
maiden address.
There, what's the story?
He is a record producer, and they
he wants to sign a contract.
No, that's Will.I.Am.
- Okay, he ...
and it's a backup singer ...
- No, he really Will.I.Am.
From Fergie.
- My God!
If I knew anything about him,
I was so excited.
Give me your phone.
- Why?
I take a picture.
- What?
Give him. You go to there.
- No.
And you're going to appoint yourself.
You are you so ashamed.
Got the picture?
You're a real freak.
That you really did.
Excuse me, Mr. and Mrs. Tripplehorn ...
Yes?
- Well, yes.
We are Tripplehorn.
Who are you, who
Questions about us?
We just wanted to here
talk to you.
And what is this about?
- You know.
Let everyone save the embarrassment,
and continue this conversation private.
But I can the rest of my
risotto with me?
For these truffles are
amazing and very expensive.
Go away. Now.
Honey, get out.
Now.
Can you just ...
A very expensive bottle.
I grab your glasses.
We move voluntarily.
Watch out.
Come on, we still
anybody hurt?
If I were you, I
say no more, bitch.
That's not nice.
- A bit dim, guys.
What are you doing?
That's my wallet.
And my phone ...
- I am now very pissed off.
Now I eat it off the ground.
I want to talk your boss now.
- That will not happen, Mr. Tripplehorn.
Or should I ...
Phil Foster say?
Use the drop when
make a reservation ...
do not use the same
aliases as your ransom letters stand.
Letters ransom?
- Did you really get away ...
Joe Miletto could steal?
Someone somewhere is making a big mistake.
Guys, this ...
- If an error.
It's a very big misunderstanding.
We are Phil and Claire Foster ...
we know nothing about ransom letters.
I assure you.
You sat at the table.
The girl in front said ...
that you were the Tripplehorn.
- No, no ...
Let me explain.
My husband thought, very sweet, but ...
delusion that we are suggesting
asked one table would have ...
but we were too late.
They were very rude.
Thus rude.
- They called to Tripplehorn ...
and we said "we!".
We took him.
So you just took the
reservation for someone else?
I was also part.
My husband has some ideas in his head ...
a sort of thing.
- I'm an idiot sometimes.
Shut up.
I think you're the Fosters.
- Thanks.
I also believe that you
aka Tripplehorn is ...
and that you are my boss his
stable property ...
and that you're too worried
to admit it.
I give you three seconds
to the Flash Drive to!
The three-seconds game?
That I play every day.
This is another version!
- A ...
That's a big mistake ...
- Two ...
God, he turned it.
A deadly shot!
Help!
- Three!
No, no. All right,
I have the Flash Drive!
What?
- That's what I thought
Where is it?
In the park.
- The park?
Be more specific.
Central Park.
This will happen:
we go together to
that Central Park ...
and you show us exactly
where it is.
Okay.
- Come on!
Why do you take us to
the most desolate spot in New York?
The weapon was turned!
- We need to people.
Maybe people here,
as gay or nachtboters.
Night Boat?
- Yes, very popular.
It is good.
We must go to the boathouse.
- Trips.
There's nobody here.
That night boat stuff
was in Seattle, I think.
Maybe I can here them
what disconcert.
Open the door.
We may have to break in,
for I have no key.
Stay here.
We need people now.
Tell them that you have a medical condition.
We drugs out of the car
need ...
that just by "a doctor
can be given.
Why?
- It's for your penis.
Intravenous drug penis,
and you're very shy.
We need to show a hospital.
- What is wrong with my penis?
Forward.
Where is it?
- The problem:
Phil has a medical condition ...
- Give them just the flash drive.
Claire, just give them.
- We need to show a hospital.
But your penis.
It is a two-step procedure
that show a nurse has to happen.
Because there is a two-step ...
- My penis is fine!
Much can penis blood.
- Show him where it is!
Come on!
- Do 's good girl.
And listening to your spouse.
- Yeah, listen to me.
I put the flash drive over in the corner.
Where? Show it.
Come on, it's not a game.
I'm going to lift a floorboard.
There.
This one.
It is here.
- Where? I do not see it.
Run!
Come on.
Here.
Come on!
Full throttle.
- This is full throttle.
Come on.
Pick it up. Run.
We are going to die!
I do not want kids
go live with your mother!
She's horrible!
- Can you see?
No!
How did this happen?
- They are not what they seem.
You guys are coming!
Is it?
Phil, come on.
We need more walk.
I'm not in bad condition.
I'm afraid.
So do I.
Ready?
Bring it on.
All of them.
My God, your blood?
- This is the Cabernet.
Sorry, you chewing gum?
Sorry, forgive me, I am
been working nine hours.
Once. Which restaurant?
- Claw.
That place in Tribeca,
with soup for $ 50?
How was that?
- Not great.
We finally have someone
reservations taken.
You took one reservation?
- Yes.
We did.
- You just took a table.
Just so?
- Shocking, huh.
During our meal come
these guys show up ...
and they said they
Joe Miletto worked.
That they said.
When we knew that.
We thought the waiters there.
So we followed them out ...
and suddenly they grab our stuff.
Therefore we have no ID.
Yes, that was very frightening.
Then came their arms above
and they asked for a flash drive.
Why grab my knee?
- Because we show appointments.
A gay couple,
met during the night boats.
God! The Bald and The Crazy.
Gay couple fucking.
We forgot our gay dinner.
Can I say something?
Joe Miletto dear husband is not ...
So if you're on his radar,
we need to talk to someone ...
No, you do not understand.
We took one reservation ...
So we must undo.
- Stop!
Put you down!
Arroyo?
- Yes?
Got a minute?
I'll be back. Make sure you
story is finished.
Forward.
Now they are dressed like cops.
Maybe they are agents.
Why are agents in
involved? What's happening?
What do we do?
- Honey.
They are going to kill us.
Dump our bodies in bags.
Breathe. Breathe?
- Only in.
Focus.
Your eyes look weird.
- I turn on. What should we do?
What should we do?
- We have to leave and go home.
We can not go home.
- I'm going home.
I'm going home.
- They have our ID. They know where we live.
My God, the children.
Will you accept a collect call from ...
My God, it smells like urine.
- Yes, I accept that.
Everything is good with children?
- Yes.
I want you to continue a bit later tonight.
That is a problem for me.
- What?
I have to go to a party.
- You talk to her.
Katie with Phil. I do not have time
to talk, I'll pay you double.
I do not think enough.
- Are you kidding?
I miss the party, but I think
that what is expensive.
I see them.
- An hour? All right.
Get the kids out of the house now.
Go out the back door, to your home.
Now it sounds a little dangerous.
- No.
That a further five charges extra.
- Fine, get the children out now.
We love them, and everything will be fine.
- All is well, tell him we love them.
Dick. Children.
- What now?
They are safe. We need a place
find a lot of people.
This whole evening was a mistake.
We are humans.
We're just a boring couple from New Jersey,
this was an idiotic idea.
It was not an idiot idea.
It was a dinner in Manhattan ...
a night where we do not all night
the children need to talk ...
and what we do next week.
- Look where it brought us.
Should we call 112?
- We are talking about Joe Miletto.
And?
- Those agents who wanted to murder us ...
who has in his pocket.
That guy owns agents.
We can not trust agent.
- What should we do?
We can not go home, not
to the police.
Miletto, why does he Tripplehorn?
Because they have the Flash Drive.
If they return the flash drive now?
- Why would they do that?
Because we will find
and we make sure they do.
If they have the Flash Drive
this is over.
Fine, I stand behind you.
I need you only one question.
Condemn me. What is a Flash Drive?
- Seriously?
Phil, I can not.
- That you put on the side of a laptop.
This is such a computer memory stick thing?
So we call in my office.
We must stick thing that computer have
to save our lives.
How? We know nothing about Tripplehorn.
- That's not quite true.
We know where to eat tonight.
Come on.
Hi, above. We have just
dinner with our friend 'Sam.I.Am.
You mean Will.I.Am?
If you call them so that's weird.
That's not nice.
We were here, and Will.I.Am thinks he
phone on the table were lying, so ...
We must look on the table.
- I must look at the phone on the table.
If you do not mind.
- You understand what I say? Look at me.
We must look for the phone on the table.
Can you look at the phone on the table?
- Fine.
This way.
- I just wasted half my life.
Look at the monitor.
He left it there on the table,
that was really a waste of time.
The King of Siam is hellish.
Thanks for your help,
I'm sarcastic.
Mother.
Claw, you're welcome.
We have a telephone. How to use
we get behind a address to come?
I think I know someone
who can help us.
What do you know this man again for?
I saw him a few houses to show
in the north.
It is a few years ago, but I remember
he was a security expert.
He eventually bought a house here
of an agent in this office.
I forgot the address, but perhaps
we can look into a file.
Got a key?
- No. May I have your coat?
Yes, you cold?
I think I can break open the lock.
If I had a hairpin can
I might get the lock open.
My God, who are you?
- Here, come on.
No, we should look.
- It takes only a little.
He called Holbrooke, Grant, do you see
in file cabinets. I look into your computer.
Come on.
Come on, rainbow wheel.
- That's a bad sound.
I got it.
- Come on, get out.
Come on.
Investigators.
Will you come and sit with me?
Why are you a nice couple
from the suburbs to the balls?
Is not that a bit lower
your price range?
This conversation would be even better
If I knew what you were talking about.
Phil and Claire Foster.
Some of your men have them
arrested tonight at Claw.
They have a lot to scare them.
You know what I'm talking about.
It tells me nothing. So unless
You want my company for tonight ...
not come back before
have an arrest warrant.
Slick, we have a problem?
This is it.
This is the place.
You may not know me anymore.
I'm Claire Foster ...
I am a real estate agent.
I told you what homes in the north show.
Yes, I remember. It is already quite late.
- I know, and I'm sorry.
This is an emergency. Can I come over here?
It is very important.
Come upstairs.
I can not believe you feel, from hundreds
customers, remember this guy.
I've always been good
with names and faces.
Your memory is fantastic, honey.
That you feel all the people you see
This reminds ...
a ...
I get flashbacks of all
all these empty houses we saw.
We have many views.
That's me.
This is my husband, Phil Foster.
- How are you?
We have some problems, and
We really need help.
I know it's late, but if
Briefly, we can come ...
it's a great story, and you
We can help you.
Please, I am your
falling far short.
Why not.
Come inside.
Sit down.
You're lucky to be alive.
I would stay away from those agents.
Therefore, we hoped you could help us.
- That's the least I can do.
You were so patient with me.
All those long trips on the toll road.
You're welcome.
This is definitely the right place for you.
The ladies love there from.
- It's okay with me.
I think you all do well.
I tell you what we must do.
We do not have much time ...
Do you have something on, then take
we are what we need, and ...
then we'll fall no more difficult.
- We have a phone ...
where we have an address, and you
yet had your own detective agency?
I practice personal protection, industrial
intelligence, government affairs, black ops ...
things like that.
There's your shirt. No wonder you
could not be found. It has to.
This is Natanya.
She is from Israel.
They do not speak much English.
Are you also have sex with us?
- No, thanks.
Thank you, no.
Goodbye.
- I met her in Tel Aviv ...
when I was working with the Mossad,
she is a sweet girl.
She seems really sweet. It was very nice
her to ask if we wanted sex.
So ...
- Give me that number only.
We have the last of
Mr. and Mrs. Foster have not seen.
Someone has an alarm
in a real estate ...
security cameras have
these included.
The file from the computer will see an address
Holbrooke Grant, West Village.
What are they doing?
- What do we have?
Small burglary.
I tried to be friendly.
- Thank you, officer friendly.
Enough for today?
- Yes, sir. See you tomorrow.
Good evening.
Will we see?
- Yes, certainly. To the broker.
See where they are more
to have looked.
Where did all this stuff come from?
- Radio Shack.
Really?
What happened to him on?
Let me see that number.
Soft hands.
Here I type the number,
Thomas Felton is an alias I think.
Whether he is a big fan of the Tripplehorn.
There is no address.
It's a cell phone.
We do not need address book.
This number locates the signal ...
- That's great, you're ...
okay instruments.
Mr. Felton's phone is located
at 135 Avenue D.
Great. Who likes shirts?
Thank you.
- It was the least I could do.
Are you expecting someone?
- This is the NYPD. We have some questions for you
These are the agents that we
attempted to murder.
So come down. I'm having sex,
I'm working.
Am I, or is that 'Fat Albert'?
What was that?
Is there another exit?
Down to my garage.
There is a service elevator next to my office ...
I keep them busy.
Go ahead.
Can we get out?
- I think so.
They are still there. Here we come
not pass. Think.
What are you doing?
You can not do.
This is Holbrooke's car.
Let's get outta here.
Do you have a better idea?
That's not really driving in the city.
This is a sports car.
Thank God that Holbrooke was there.
- Yes.
Thank God.
Holbrooke hell out really late.
- Sorry?
What was that? Who were you there?
Who is this person?
That giggling flirting charming person?
- What are you talking about?
When you look on him,
explained to you.
If a spark sparking.
- That's not true.
True. And I understand.
Because I also explained.
He is super seksie. And why
muscles on your shoulders you need?
That way.
And I'm the man but.
I'm just an idiot who does not know
how to load the dishwasher.
I'm the guy who needs more training.
Who should light the man?
- I had forgotten to explain to you.
This is ...
- Why do I always forget?
I remember.
I am every day ...
make breakfast, go to work,
come home, clean the house clean ...
remove the children, bring and fetch them
football, cooking dinner ...
over dinner, tuck them in the bath,
pull their panties to ...
that's a battle every night, the
is always a big surprise ...
every night they have a pajamas,
and after I everyone ...
and eat snot to me washed I use
I have the energy I have left ...
for myself physically in our bed to lay in
rather to highlight for you.
Let's stop.
This is a great time to ...
Yes, we should stop.
I know you work hard.
But you know what all that hard work
would make ten times easier?
I.
If you would trust me occasionally to
things to address. But you do not.
You should do yourself, your way.
I do everything at this stage to error,
even before I even get a chance.
If you let me do something for you,
I think ...
I will leave you amazed.
I know I will leave you amazed.
You think I do not hear myself, I
enjoy it like a bitch to come?
Hailey and Brad want to divorce.
- I know.
Have you ever thought about
to leave with me?
No.
You've never fantasized about me
leaving for another man?
No. I fantasize sometimes about
to be alone.
What do you mean?
- There are times ...
I thought about it,
on my worst days ...
to leave.
And then to book a hotel ...
and alone in a quiet room to be
with air conditioning ...
sitting down to eat my lunch with anyone
that touches me ...
Light and then a Sprite to drink.
All alone.
- That sounds terrible.
I just want a day that is not from
depends on how the days of all others expired.
I do not have dirty sex fantasy or something.
That I would understand.
Everyone has dirty sex fantasies.
Those of you is clear with Holbrooke.
Mine with Cyndi Lauper.
Really? In the past or present.
- Any time of day.
What an interesting choice.
Brad told me that everything was fine
with him and Hailey.
And they really excellent
were roommates.
We have not, right?
- No.
Right?
We have to move.
135 Avenue D. Here it is.
I park here.
They are not home.
We wait.
- How long?
The agents who were Holbrooke
can now go on this way.
The fourth floor.
What are you doing?
- If we Tripplehorn not find ...
we might even find their Flash Drive.
Come here.
We can do it.
- Am I dressed up one night.
Ready?
One, two, three, go!
Give everything.
Everything you do, I do high heels.
I want you to think about it.
They have a chicken with
crushed with a highlighter.
These are bad people.
Look you there, I look here.
Damn, Phil.
- What?
Why do you never shut the drawers?
- I'm sorry.
You never close to a la
you've opened.
Do not move.
Who is it?
- Now move.
This is not as it looks.
- Look here for.
He has broken my neck.
- Stop it.
We can explain everything.
- What are you doing here?
Sit down.
Hurry up you two.
Careful.
You must be Thomas Felton?
People call me 'Taste'.
I think the people you
Tripplehorn call.
I'm a big fan of Jane Tripplehorn.
- Yes, she's a great actress.
Who is this?
- I'm Whippet.
Whippet like a dog?
No, as you come from a nitric
cream sucks.
Stupid bitch.
- Have you ever contacted your mother?
This is a beautiful thing.
Are we going to duel with ten steps?
Zip your mouth shut.
- My head zip up?
Really?
- He said "zip your mouth shut."
Is that your best 'tough guy sense?
You heard me. Unzip your face shut.
- Zipper you vagina but close, Raymond Burke.
I do not know how I should respond.
'F' you.
- 'F' me, 'F' you.
- 'F' you. What are you doing here?
'F' you, fucking fucker.
What do you want?
- You have no idea what you've done to us.
What?
When you were in your reservation Claw missed
You've ruined our lives.
What are you talking about?
- We have missed nothing.
We saw the two gangsters Case
check, so we have gone away.
Are you the reservation police?
- What will you tell?
We had not booked,
So we have taken from you.
And now they think that we you are.
You have made our reservations?
Who does that?
What people are you?
Come on.
- How did you find our way?
I need your number stolen
the reservation list.
That is smart.
- Thank you.
Have you used our real number
make a reservation?
Not home, but the cell phone.
That is brilliant.
You're really a criminal genius.
So I'm an asshole all the time?
I can not live up to things you think?
Yes.
- I can not do anything right?
I buy the wrong soft drinks,
the wrong beer ...
I hear you, man.
- The wrong nipple clamps.
These clips made me hurt.
And when I come home, watch me
not even.
I have to beg for sex.
As if it is a gift.
And forget the back but.
Forget that.
- That has been forgotten.
I'm sorry if what I am tired,
after having worked all night.
And then come home, you jumping,
and give you a free lapdance.
Sorry. I was very happy to strip
and make money at the Hippo.
It made me feel good.
I earned money.
But you should be greedy ...
and began to steal everything from everyone.
- That's enough.
Sorry I dream. I do not want the rest
of my life stolen car seats sold.
I think you're losing control.
My dream then? And me?
- Stop arguing.
Stop arguing.
Everybody valve.
Dampers close.
- Be quiet.
These gangsters were behind us, because
they think we have a flash drive ...
that you have stolen from them.
You go to so far ...
and tell them that you
The Tripplehorn are.
Wait a minute, bitch.
- Do not call me bitch, whore.
Are thugs who now follow you?
- Have you not heard what I said, whore?
Why we are here.
You need us anything.
We must now get outta here.
Whippet, honey, 2 minutes.
Ready? Hurry.
Hurry.
- You can not leave.
Forget Latex.
Only the most important.
Stop suits, no one
going somewhere.
Stop. You take up too much of.
- What are you doing?
Nothing you don
30 seconds lost.
Bobby De Niro, a classic.
Really. You are going nowhere.
Stop. Nobody goes somewhere.
Watch me.
This we do.
We take the flash drive, and you bring ...
- Take him yourself.
Honey, we're off.
- Yes.
I'm done. Here.
Come on.
- Wait.
Maybe not a good idea to leave.
This is our home.
No, it's not.
This is your house.
Come home.
How do we bring this to Miletto?
Joe Miletto. The boy who blackmails you.
You're far from home, or not?
- What do you mean to them?
Nice evening.
That's not gone
as I had expected.
Come on. Did you see how her tongde?
- Yes.
Welcome, officers.
Are you Holbrooke Grant?
- Yes.
Want some clothes?
- No.
It's late and I have already told everything
against other agents.
Wait. What other agents?
What did that when he said Taste
we were far from home?
He is called "Taste".
I would not attract much.
What is this?
- Gun.
This is a fucking gun.
Take care.
- Do not shout. I know what I do.
It's one way.
- I'm sorry.
I am sorry Wait.
What are you doing?
- Wait.
We need you to pick us.
We need as quickly as possible, Phil.
That does not work.
- Put him in the back, asshole.
You put him in reverse.
Put it in reverse.
In reverse.
There is someone pissed off.
It seems that they come with us.
Why I drive backwards?
Take your foot off the brake.
- No.
Come on.
Put your foot on the brake.
- No, I did not get off.
Take the wheel.
- What?
Just do.
He would not release the brake.
No.
You owe me one, eh?
Take a side with your ass.
Move on.
We get some.
Why do they want us
so like murder?
Do you have a computer or a BlackBerry?
I have a Candle.
- Give.
It's a gift. Not break.
- Really?
I had to cry.
And the morning we walk
the birds of change
This is Crenshaw.
The DA.
Claire, we need the street.
- Why?
If I 'right' hey, go right.
I have a plan.
Now!
This is the NYPD.
The street is closed.
Convert your car immediately stopped.
Great, Phil.
- I had to try something.
I thought I had a plan.
- I love you, but your plans do not work.
Ensure you that you "married people
stuff "to get a list ...
if my life is at stake.
When I press the horn,
You press on the brake ...
your wife switches.
And you kicked him.
This will work.
- We got him!
Well, folks,
one, two, three ...
Stop the vehicle.
- Now!
What did I tell you?
And now to put aside
then we can ...
The brake does not work.
- The brake does not work?
The brakes are gone.
Since you're pretty done with it.
I'm leaving.
Fine, until later.
I Manker nothing.
Come on.
Well done sweetie.
You're doing good.
Is everything okay?
- Cold.
The Flash Drive is gone.
The Tripplehorn are gone.
We have nothing.
Let's see if
there is a blanket in the car.
I am curious to hear
what happened here.
While we sit drinking a beer,
there are two people inside the bar ...
The two people you've just let go.
The Fosters?
The Fosters.
You have a good memory.
But they come in and so on
we know they will shoot at us.
Mr. Foster? Tax lawyer
was armed?
That is strange.
- That's weird.
It is also dangerous,
so we chased them.
You know what, well done.
Go home.
If you want we can continue
detect them.
Nice evening.
We have understood.
- Say your prayers but.
What was at
computer stick that thing?
What great books and photographs.
Pictures of what?
- Services rendered.
And one of Joe's Milletto clubs
Peppermint Hippo named.
But that does not get out now, that computer
Stick thing is at the bottom of river.
And we will finish
as agents find us.
Explain to me one more time ...
Honey!
- If I get shot ...
I would like to know why that is.
What are you laughing at?
- I think it's nice, but we are not really ...
shot.
- I think so.
I do not think so.
The strange thing is that Ledger had only
but photographs and information from a customer.
Crenshaw DA.
- That guy with the broom?
The Tripplehorn may have
Flash Drive Miletto stolen ...
but they pressed the DA off.
Taste therefore reacted so strangely
Miletto about when you started.
I see.
Does it have anything to do with Crenshaw?
But there is definitely something to do
Crenshaw with ...
He is the key. And we must
find a way to come to Crenshaw.
The Tripplehorn have him
at the Peppermint Hippo found.
And we are Tripplehorn's?
We are, yes.
We could use some help.
- Waxing, of course.
Is that my tracksuit?
Yes, that was in the trunk of your Audi ...
and which is now parked at the
East River ...
and he can now use a beurtje ...
which I do in the next
decades programs will repay ...
centuries old gun like that
I've taken ...
who is also proved useless.
He just popped apart.
- But for that reason we are not here.
How unreal all this is
may sound ...
you after we have seen our
evening only become stranger ...
There were cars that were stuck together.
One of those cars was yours ...
I myself have a quite interesting
evening and I am very tired ...
how fun it is you again,
would rather go to somebody else's door.
I just wanted my wife to dinner ...
I was hoping we could one evening
with the feeling of yesteryear ...
but now I only go home.
Now that I have a plan to
pull it off ...
my plans are generally not
so good, but now I have one ...
and I need help.
Although I would commit suicide if I
muscle bundle to your look ...
and your girlfriend is so beautiful that it seems
like a glittering jet looks ...
yet I know and believe I
that a person in there is ...
who understands exactly
I now must make.
So please, Holbrooke,
can we come?
Give us the chance to explain your
what we want ...
and want to fuck
a shirt?
Come on.
Here it is, you know the plan yet?
- Hardly.
Let us inside. It is new,
they must work tonight.
I do not know what you're talking about.
- I'm the new girl.
Really?
And who are you?
I'm her pimp.
- You're her pimp?
Yeah asshole, he is my pimp,
I can now work ...
or should I call Joe Miletto
to say that his later, Piccolo?
I have no gum.
The locker room is left.
- Come on, pimp.
Wait here.
- Where are you going?
That must be a monkey.
Hey, I'm still down a man,
do you think?
Sorry I ...
my God!
I know,
never mind.
You look really great.
Why is it so clear,
it should still be dark and dim ...
just love to take a 40 year
old stripper / mother.
Do your breasts once.
- I had to attract opposite ...
and then run. By
I think I lost a nipple.
No, you look great.
- Really?
Really.
This was the only long enough
was to cover my caesarean.
I keep looking at your breasts.
Let's go.
I want you to buy.
This is the end of days stuff.
Honey, I think I can not.
Of course you do this, you are
a beautiful strong woman ...
you are the mother of my children.
I want you to go inside ...
and let the Gucci pop.
These Gucci pop it,
and then we can go home.
Come on you can do it.
- I can.
If you just want to look up.
Fine, you can enter.
No, you both.
He likes you too nice.
Someone pointed out by the pervert.
- I can not.
Yes, because you are a beautiful
husband and the father of my children ...
So you go in there
and revolves around that pole as a refugee.
There he is with those sunglasses.
What happened to him by the hand
that's dirty, that he do not need.
Enough junk to clean.
Can I help you?
- We are here for Crenshaw.
You can only join him in the neighborhood
if he chooses you.
Choose, for what?
Carlton, go again to step aside.
I think you avoid okay, honey.
A wild western, lounge-like.
Without syphilis.
You have a big mouth,
I think that's fine.
And have your friend androgenouse
included.
Is he a man or a woman.
I do not know.
I'll let you guess.
It's very sexy.
Why do not you two see here
what you can.
I think he wants us to
him to dance.
If it does, we must better
do the fast version.
Go ahead, if you spend time with me
want, you deserve it.
So go there but are.
Women to one side please.
Actually we are not ...
we do not like dancing,
We prefer to talk with you ...
and then remain relatively quiet.
We want to talk to you.
- I am not here to talk ...
whether you leave or go dancing.
What is it?
I do not feel it.
Carlton, if you like ...
their education as the door, please.
We're just warming up,
Now we will feel the heat.
We are now going to happen.
Now we go!
- Count on that!
Now the hot and wild.
Where he takes her to?
Phil are not going to surrender.
What will they do?
Sex robots.
Come here, you two.
We have something you want.
- I know for sure.
How much for a night?
- $ 100,000.
That's quite a bit. I know of no
Women who are worth so much.
How about a woman with
a Flash Drive?
How are you?
We are Tripplehorn.
They just keep coming with those weapons.
Why do not we take a walk
to talk about.
Private.
This was so beautiful can be.
This is part of the plan right?
I must go back into the underground
for a refresher.
Let's keep this simple ...
you give me the Flash Drive or Collins
breaks both arms of your wife.
I have the flash drive hidden where nobody
will find him ...
Holbrooke if Grant is not the hour
learn from us, until we are safe ...
He will drive the content of that
disclose.
He is the ex-soldier
We have interviewed the last night ...
He is real.
What's going on?
Sorry, we seek a roof thing '
account, it only takes a minute.
No, you get a minute.
This is my roof, baby.
It is good Claire, we
they expect.
We are really lost.
They were just about
Joe leave ...
they have someone on hand with
The flash drive is nothing to get here.
Have you seen the flash drive?
Do not worry,
We will say nothing about those pictures.
Shut up.
- What kind of photos?
Nothing.
- Does he not?
What I do not know?
- I think I said too much.
Sorry, but I can understand why you
pornographic pictures of the DA have ...
you never know
when they come in handy.
Close your mouth, Skippy.
- Connect your vagina but you.
No, if he says vagina,
he means your face.
You have said that what those Flash Drive
stood with city contracts ...
that way you wiped clean.
All this time I keep the police away from you ...
while you dirty pictures of me kept?
- Very dirty pictures.
You could sit in jail if not for me
was. So watch your tone, Mr. DA.
You have something to talk
So my wife and I give you that room.
Nobody move there because it is a piece
easier if someone dies.
As with "The Kill Shot".
Put the gun down!
- Come on, policeman.
It's okay.
- This is not good this is a bad idea.
Now shoot me.
- It will go on shooting anyone.
Claire, look at me ...
look at me!
I have this under control ...
I got this under control.
Count to three.
- What?
Just count.
- No, that does not work with adults with weapons.
Trust me on this one.
I've had enough ...
my kids will have 90 minutes
awake, so it stops here ...
I count to three and then made everyone
weapons.
Does she seriously?
A.
- I think she thinks.
Two.
- They're kidding right?
Three.
This is the NYPD, let your arms fall
and hands in the air.
Let your arms fall
I'm a cop.
- No, not anymore.
I told you I could surprise you.
Well you see again, Detective.
You also Mr. Foster.
- This was part of the plan?
The helicopter and the SWAT team
are all part of your plan?
Your friend Holbrooke has called me to
here to be 5.30 ...
you've got something for me?
- Yes, that's right.
I think that getting up enough
to those two a while to close.
Thank you.
Mr. Miletto, Mr. DA ...
you two are under arrest,
for obstruction of justice ...
extortion, conspiracy and I believe
including prostitution.
Move them out.
Do you need a ride?
Yes please, our children will
is it bad frightened.
No, we have sent somebody,
They are wonderful to sleep with the babysitter.
Thank God.
What is your story?
Just a boring married couple from
New Jersey.
So what about that elevator.
I actually had my wife
dinner in the city promised.
I'm not sure but I think this
the best pancake I've ever had.
How did you come to that plan?
It's like that book
the book club ...
Nasrin ensures that her brother and
stepfather to squabble ...
so they can be off to
pulling through the desert ...
and peace can menstruate.
What?
- You read the book?
Of course. I have them all
read.
Why?
- Because you care about.
I only read the first 30
and the last page.
Who has time to read. I love
not even of those books.
What? I sit here a little?
I would do so again.
Tonight, no,
that was very dangerous.
Not so much tonight. Just us.
You and me, the kids, everything.
I would do so again.
I would choose you every time again.
"Hope You've Liked & Enjoyed The Movie"
Copyright from SI Media
<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<
>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>
>><<@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@  >><<
>><<@@@@@@@@@sssssssss@@@@@@  iiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@mmmmmmmmm@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@ >><<
>><<@@@@@@  ssssssssssssssss@@@@@iiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@mmmmmmmmm@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@mmmmmmmmm@@@@@@@@@@@@@@eeee@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@   dddddd@@@@@@@@@@iiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa@@@@@@@ >><<
>><<@@@@@ssssssssssssssssssss@@@@ iiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@mmmmmmmmm@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@mmmmmmmmm@@@@@@@@@@@@eeeeeeeeee@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@  dddddd@@@@@@@@  iiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa@@@@@@@   >><<
>><<@@@@  ssssssssssssssssssssss@@@@@@@iiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@@@mmmmm   mmmm@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@mmmm  mmmmm@@@@@@@@@eeeeeeeeeeeeeee@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@   dddddd@@@@@@@@ iiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@aaaaaaa@@@@@@@@@aaaaaaa@@@@@@@   >><<
>><<@@@@sssssss@@@@@sssssss@@@@@@@iiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@@@mmmmm@mmmm@@@@@@@@@@@@@@mmmm@  mmmmm@@@@@@@eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@dddddd@@@@@@@@@@iiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@  aaaaaaaaa@@@@@@@  >><<
>><<@@@@sssssss@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@iiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@@@mmmmm@  mmmm@@@@@@@@@@@@@mmmm@    mmmmm@@@@@eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@ dddddd@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@   aaaaaaaaaaaaaa@@@@@@@  >><<
>><<@@@@ ssssssss@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@iiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@@@mmmmm@@mmmm@@@@@@@@@@@@mmmm@@   mmmmm@@@@@eeeeeee@@@@eeeeeeee@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@  dddddd@@@@@@@@@@ iiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@@@@@aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa@@@@@@@  >><<
>><<@@@@@ssssssss@@@@@@@@@@@@@@ iiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@@@mmmmm@@@mmmm@@@@@@@@@@mmmm@@@   mmmmm@@@@eeeeeeee@@@@eeeeeeee@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@ dddddddd@@@@@@@@@@ iiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@@@aaaaaaaaaaaa  aaaaaaaaa@@@@@@@  >><<
>><<@@@@@@ssssssss@@@@@@@@@@@@@ iiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@@@mmmmm@@@ mmmm@@@@@@@@@mmmm@@@@  mmmmm@@@@eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee@@@@@@@@@@@@@@ ddddddddddd@@@@@@@@@@ iiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@aaaaaaaaaaaaa@@@ aaaaaaa@@@@@@@  >><<
>><<@@@@@@@ sssssssss@@@@@@@@@@@ iiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@@@mmmmm@@@@mmmm@@@@@@@@mmmm@@@@@mmmmm@@@@eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee@@@@@@@@@@@@  ddddddddddddddd@@@@@@@@@@ iiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@aaaaaaaaaaaa@@@@@ aaaaaaaa@@@@@@@  >><<
>><<@@@@@@@@ sssssssss@@@@@@@@@@ iiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@@@mmmmm@@@@ mmmm@@@@@@@mmmm@@@@@   mmmmm@@@@eeeeeeeeeeeeeeee@@@@@@@@@@@@ dddddddddddddddddd@@@@@@@@@@ iiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@aaaaaaaaaaaa@@@@@@ aaaaaaaa@@@@@@@  >><<
>><<@@@@@@@@@@ sssssss@@@@@@@@@ iiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@@@mmmmm@@@@@mmmm@@@@@@mmmm@@@@@@ mmmmm@@@@eeeeeeeeeee@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@ddddddd@@@@@dddddd@@@@@@@@@@iiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@aaaaaaaaaaa@@@@@@@aaaaaaaa@@@@@@@ >><<
>><<@@@@@@@@@@  sssssss@@@@@@@@@iiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@@@mmmmm@@@@@@mmmm@@@@mmmm@@@@@@@ mmmmm@@@@eeeeeee@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@ddddddd@@@@@@dddddd@@@@@@@@@@iiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@aaaaaaaaaa@@@@@@@  aaaaaaaa@@@@@@@ >><<
>><<@@@@@@@@@@  sssssss@@@@@@@@@iiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@@@mmmmm@@@@@@  mmmm@@@mmmm@@@@@@@  mmmmm@@@@@eeeeeee@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@ddddddd@@@@@@dddddd@@@@@@@@@@iiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@aaaaaaaaa@@@@@@aaaaaaaaaa@@@@@@@ >><<
>><<@@@@@@@@@ sssssssss@@@@@@@@@iiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@@@mmmmm@@@@@@@ mmmm@@mmmm@@@@@@@@mmmmm@@@@@@eeeeeee@@@@@eeeee@@@@@@ddddddd@@@@@@ dddddd@@@@@@@@@@ iiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@ aaaaaaaaa@@@  aaaaaaaaaaaa@@@@@@@>><<
>><<@@@@@ssssssssssssssss@@@@@@iiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@mmmmm@@@@@@@@mmmm   mmmm@@@@@@@@  mmmmm@@@@@@@eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee@@@@@@@dddddddddddddddddddd@@@@@@@@@@ iiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa@@@@@@ >><<
>><<@@@@@sssssssssssss@@@@@@@  iiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@mmmmmmm@@@@@@@mmmmmmmm@@@@@@@@mmmmmmm@@@@@@@eeeeeeeeeeeeee@@@@@@@@@ddddddddddddddddddd@@@@@@@@@  iiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@  aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa@@@@@@>><<
>><<@@@@@ssssssssss@@@@@@@@@ iiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@ mmmmmmmm@@@@@@  mmmmmmmm@@@@@@@ mmmmmmmm@@@@@@@@@@eeeeee@@@@@@@@@@@@@@dddddddddddddddd@@@@@@@@   iiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii@@@@@@@@@@@aaaaaa@@@@aaaaaaaaaaaa@@@@  >><<
>><<@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@   >><<
<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<<
>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>